In Ma'am Rebecca's room,
she has a teddy bear.
Then, there's a spy camera.
I'm sure it recorded
what really happened.
Oh, no! I saw it earlier
when I was cleaning.
It was already thrown
in the trash.
Stay here first, okay?
So no one can see you.
I know you need someone.
That's why I'm here.
Just like before,
when something happened to her.
No, you weren't there.
You left.
Ma'am, I have something
to tell you.
Just remember,
do not trust Tomas.
Is everything okay?
What I was going to say
isn't really important.
I'll just say it later.
["NEVER SAY DIE" BY KIM DE LEON
PLAYING]
I know.
I left.
And I shouldn't have.
I was selfish for choosing
to prioritize my career.
When I know
that you're still reeling
from what happened to auntie
even though you were already
making a name for yourself.
Don't call it selfishness.
What you did was right.
Because if you stayed
knowing you didn't
really want to,
I would've been hurt even more.
But it's okay now.
I understand.
But this time,
I want to do it right, Andrew.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't want you to be
or feel alone.
I want to be here for you.
So, what's the difference
between afritada and mechado ?
They both have...
- Tomato sauce?
- Joey.
Kyle, Elai.
Hi, Joey.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
You visited Andrew?
Yes, he still has work.
Yes.
Every time you say that to me,
I remember how much I needed you
before.
When something happened
to mommy before,
I kept telling myself...
I could handle it.
I couldn't allow myself
to be hurt. I'm a man, right?
But now,
I don't know if I can accept
that maybe...
she might really be gone.
You know...
We really don't know
what lies ahead.
But knowing that there's someone
you can lean on
during hard times like this,
Andrew, I'm sure about that.
I will not leave you.
I'm right here. Never again.
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL MUSIC
PLAYING]
Is he still in the garden?
Is he still there?
He went down, I think...
- He went down, right?
- He went down.
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL MUSIC
CONTINUES]
Yeah.
I'll just go to him.
Take care.
You too.
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL MUSIC
CONTINUES]
She said take care, Ma'am.
We weren't careful.
I already saw him.
I just looked away for a moment,
suddenly he was gone.
I didn't see anyone leave, Sir.
I didn't even see anyone
come in.
Could it be that he passed
through the carwash, Sir?
Possible.
But at least now,
we know where to find them.
Maybe we don't need
that carwash anymore, Sir.
Looks like we'll get a good tip
from the one
you asked me to find.
I already saw him.
He's on his way here now, Major.
This is really hard
to investigate, Sir.
It's been eight years already.
I caught a Korean,
a syndicate member,
a drug pusher.
He was jailed in Korea too.
When he was released, he set up
operations here in our country.
Could he help us, Major?
This is his social media
account.
His name is Jung Tae-Sik.
Miguel!
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Bravo, bravo, bravo.
While we're struggling,
you go missing.
I thought you wanted
to show off?
- What?
- Enough, Matias!
Finish that.
You might be late.
I'll take care of this.
Let's go.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
What's wrong, Joey?
Why are you affected?
Weren't you annoyed with him?
Weren't you fighting?
You disliked him, right?
Why don't you just go back
to those feelings?
Just think you were never close.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Just think you never went
through anything together,
never shared anything.
They say when you're greeted
by a bright sky,
there's a beautiful surprise
waiting for you.
Just think you never fell
for him.
[SPLASHES]
I already love someone else.
Why am I being like this?
[SOBBING]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
We had a syndicate
in South Korea before.
Like here in the Philippines,
we also had a rival group.
He was just a teenager
at that time.
But the most frightening thing
about him is...
he wasn't afraid.
Why wasn't he afraid?
I'm telling you, Theresa.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Pull your investment out now.
And let's go back to Korea,
please...
before I lose control.
Because I swear
I will kill that bastard!
I gave you every opportunity
and you wasted all of them.
And now, you want me
to treat you like an equal?
We are equals.
We always were.
But now...
You even talk to me
like I work for you.
This is not Korea.
Here, respect is earned.
He could fight and keep on
with the older ones.
And while things were chaotic,
even if it was just
a simple strike
with a blunt object
or a blow to the head,
he never hesitates.
That means he was exposed
to violence early.
Exactly.
He was different
when he took a hit.
That's why when I received
the photograph you sent,
there was no doubt,
I recognized him immediately.
He's that kid.
He's that boy.
I've told you many times
on exactly how you can
put yourself
in Berdugo's radar,
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
and you ignored
every single one.
So if you can't prove yourself,
then yes, you can go back
to Korea.
Dead or alive,
it won't matter to me.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
If he's been in the syndicate
since he was young,
like you said,
so why doesn't his name appear
in our files?
Could it be that his name
is different?
His name is not real.
It's a fake name.
What's his name?
Kang Dae-Hyun.
This is him.
But it's written in Korean.
Can you translate?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
“Drug suspect gone missing
after police raid”
Sir, Sir Andrew.
Miss Clarissa...
Thank you so much
for visiting mommy.
I'm sure she appreciates it.
I know she's happy
that you're here.
Where's Joey?
You haven't seen each other yet?
You haven't talked yet?
She went to see you
in the garden.
I didn't see her there.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, I'll just go back
to her there.
No need.
I'll just call her.
I'll just tell her you're here.
Excuse me.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES♪]
Mom?
Joey...
where are you?
Sir Andrew is here.
He said you didn't get to talk.
What happened?
I didn't catch him, Mom.
Why? Where did you go?
I just went out
for a while, Mom,
because I needed
to buy something,
but I'll come back right away.
Okay.
Be careful.
Okay, Mom.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're okay now, Joey.
You're okay now.
Don't you have more things
to worry about than that?
You're okay now.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
What?
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello, Joey?
Jin Ho?
I knew it.
That's why I was restless.
That damn Jin Ho.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Does this mean he's connected
to Berdugo's group?
We don't know if he's an ally
or an enemy.
But I'm sure he's not a cop.
He's part of a syndicate.
We'll use him
to get closer to Berdugo.
Make an initial report for chief
so this surveillance
becomes official.
Yes, Major.
But didn't you mention
he's a friend of your daughter,
Joey?
[LIGHT AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Dad, there's...
Joey, listen carefully.
This is about your friend,
Jin Ho.
What?
He's not really
a Korean police officer.
He's a criminal.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
What did you say, Dad?
Where did you get that?
Joey, I have evidence.
He's a syndicate member.
That means...
he cannot be trusted.
Don't go with him.
[UNEASY MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Did you hear what I said?
Dad, let's just talk later.
Okay.
Joey!
Joey...
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING♪]
How are you?
Where have you been?
You owe us a lot of stories.
We don't know
what happened to you.
Joey, how are you?
I'm so glad that you're here.
I missed you...
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
and the guys, you know.
And I'm sorry
if I haven't been in touch,
and I know that I have a lot
of explaining to do.
Yeah, we don't know
what happened to you.
We were worried about you.
We? Wait...
Are the guys here too? Where?
No, it's just me today.
Okay.
You know,
it would have been nice
to have a little reunion.
All of us together,
just like before.
Yeah.
We thought you went to Korea
without saying goodbye first.
I never left.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
But let's not talk
about me today.
What about you? How are you?
How's Peter?
And what about your Boss Idol,
Andrew?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
So, I started investigating
mom's case.
So, it's either the medicine
she took was expired,
which it wasn't,
or the dose was just too much.
Maybe there were other medicines
that shouldn't be taken together
because, if that happens,
there are side effects?
I asked the doctor.
She said there was none.
So, it's either Aunt Rebecca
didn't notice
that she took too much medicine
or she did it on purpose?
Hey, no way.
Why? I'm just saying.
Boss, sorry, okay?
I didn't mean anything bad.
I know mommy.
I know she would never do that.
I know her as a fighter,
not a quitter.
And it's not like someone
did that in your house, right?
That seems impossible.
You can trust the people
in your house, right?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, why did you go quiet?
Is there something wrong?
How's mom?
They said her room
is being prepared
so she can be transferred
from the ICU.
She's out of danger.
Really? That's good news.
Well, not quite, Yvette.
She still hasn't woken up.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew's a bit busy.
You, how are you?
Did you catch Theresa?
Yeah, you can say that.
Oh, so you got a new assignment?
You guessed it right,
but I can't tell you
the details.
Wow, keeping secrets from me.
You don't have to do that.
What? Not even a little
information? Nothing?
Okay.
So, here's the truth.
You know, yes, I've been busy
because I'm working
on something new.
That's why I haven't
had the chance
to check on all of you.
What is it?
You can tell me.
You can trust me.
I mean...
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Wait.
Sorry.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Joey...
I have to go.
Already?
Yeah, I know, but...
Duty calls.
But I promise
to make it up to you soon.
Maybe the guys
could join us too.
But now, I really have to go.
Okay.
It's really nice
to see you again, Joey.
Yeah, take care.
- See you.
Bye.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Thanks, Doc.
Okay, I'll leave you for now.
Ma'am...
do you have anything else
you want me to do?
I just need to do something.
Nothing more.
Okay, thank you.
Yes.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
What's wrong, Andrew?
Yvette, I still can't figure out
how this happened to mommy.
Yvette, I know in my heart
that she could never do this
to herself.
So, who? Who would do this?
I know everyone
who comes close to mommy.
If someone was at fault,
I'm sure it wasn't done
intentionally, Andrew.
Right, Hon?
We will never know
until she wakes up.
Right now, what's important
is our prayers
that she gets through this.
And us...
we should stay strong for her.
That's right.
So, stop asking questions
like that, Andrew, okay?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Who should I believe?
Dad wouldn't lie to me.
Maybe his intel was just wrong.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
But Jin Ho has a secret
he doesn't want to tell me.
Who should I believe?
It's hard...
[LIGHT PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello?
Okay, let's just talk later.
Okay. Bye, bye.
It's hard not having someone
to talk to.
[LIGHT PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOFT UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING]
Boss Idol.
Miss Clarissa.
I've already prepared dinner.
Will you be having dinner here?
No. How about you?
I'll just eat at home.
I'll go ahead.
Oh, about Joey...
How is she?
She's okay.
You still haven't talked?
Not yet.
Just call her.
I'll go ahead.
Take care, okay?
[DREAMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[DREAMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Hi!
- Hi.
Missed me?
[DREAMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's really hard to believe,
Dad.
Can your source
really be trusted
about what they're saying
about Jin Ho?
Maybe it's just fake news.
His name isn't even Jin Ho.
It's Kang Dae-Hyun.
And how many times
do I have to tell you?
That's what was reported to us.
Why don't you believe it?
Because, Dad, even if that man
is cranky, I trust him
because he's saved my life
several times.
I thought maybe...
he's undercover for a mission.
And they just suspected
he was part of the syndicate?
But what if it's true?
I suspect it's connected
to the syndicate
here in the Philippines.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe he's a supplier or buyer
of those coming from Korea.
I think he knows Berdugo.
How can we find that out?
What if we confront him?
- I'll call him.
- Wait, don't.
I thought of another way.
And no one else should know
about this,
not even Andrew.
Because he might report it
on Tirada,
and the syndicate
might find out.
[PHONE RINGING]
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello?
[BRAZEN MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
I also want to meet the one
you brought into our group.
Matias said he doesn't trust
that man.
That Matias doesn't trust
anyone.
Are you sure that's the Korean
we're looking for?
I'll go with you.
I really just want to see
if what you're saying
about Jin Ho is true,
that he's a criminal
and part of Berdugo's syndicate.
Who is he talking to?
Let's follow him.
Who were here the other day?
It was me, Ma'am Clarissa,
the kids, Ma'am Yvette,
and Sir Tomas.
It's broken. I'm sorry.
Let me see.
I got this from inside.
Looks like a camera.